# Ye Yint Aung

## Email | Portfolio | GitHub | LinkedIn

#### **CAREER SUMMARY**

I am a Frontend + Backend developer with industry experience building websites and web applications. I specialize in JavaScript, Vuejs and have professional experience working with PHP and Laravel. I also have experience working with Nuxt.js, HTML/Sass and React.

Working in the industry since 2018 and developing HR web-based software at BetterHR.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **BetterHR**

It is a mobile-first cloud-based **HR** solution made for companies that are ready to take on the future.

NOV 2019 – PRESENT WEB FULL STACK DEVELOPER JAN 2019 – OCT 2019 WEB DEVELOPER

- Website and software application designing, building, or maintaining.
- Develop web and mobile applications.
- Working closely with other developers, business and systems analysts.

#### nexlabs

A digital agency focuses on integrated marketing, websites, apps, UX consultancy, branding. Parent company of betterHR which is one of the best selling mobile-first cloud-based HR solutions in local.

JAN 2018 – DEC 2018 JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- Assisting the web development team with all aspects of website and application design.
- Brainstorming new tech applications such as digital storage and mobile technology.
- Collaborating with developers to implement new web features.

#### SKILL

<u> </u>	
Web Design	HTML, Markdown, CSS, Bootstrap, Element UI
Front-End	JavaScript, jQuery, Vue.js, Nuxt.js
Backend	PHP, Laravel
DBMS	MySQL
Package Manager	NPM, Yarn, Composer
Tooling	Git, SSH, Bash, GitLab CI/CD

### **EDUCATION**

**DAGON UNIVERSITY** 

2015 - 2019

Bachelor of Computer Science (B.Sc Computer Science)

<u>Seameo Chat - Seameo Regional Centre for History</u> 2019 – Current

Diploma in English